Can there be peace?
Not in my generation.
Maybe in my childs, in your generation, will be peace.
Not in ours,
there will be no peace.
We have to make
a good life before we are doing the peace,
we have to make a good life here, and there.
I don't care
if Muhammad will be Muslim or Christian
or Bedouin or Jew or everything.
I don't care.
I want him to be whatever he wants.
But you have to to know,
I have to make him think
that I want to be a Jew in Israel, in Kfar Aza,
and I want to live here.
If I'll be able to make him think in this way
there will be peace.
40, 30 years from now, maybe.
It's no matter:
I don't want to go
to the market in Gaza.
I have it in Be'er Scheva,
I have it in Ashkelon, I have it in Sderot.
It's ok.
I will not go to the sea in Gaza.
Beautiful beach, in Gaza.
If I want a good place,
I will go to Germany.
I have all the world, but I want to live here.
I want that my home will be the place that I'm going from,
from my home I will go to Stuttgart,
I will go to, where are you from?
Würzburg
I will go to Würzburg!
But from here.
This is my home. I want to live here.
I want to live good.
I want
to let my grandchild live here
in a good life.
I don't want him to be afraid from every boom.
And he his.